[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "wie",
    "answer": "as",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "ich",
    "answer": "I",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "seine",
    "answer": "his",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "dass",
    "answer": "that",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "er",
    "answer": "he",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "war",
    "answer": "was",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "für",
    "answer": "for",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "auf",
    "answer": "on",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "sind",
    "answer": "are",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "mit",
    "answer": "with",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "sie",
    "answer": "they",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "sein",
    "answer": "be",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "bei",
    "answer": "at",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "ein",
    "answer": "one",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "haben",
    "answer": "have",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "dies",
    "answer": "this",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "aus",
    "answer": "from",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "durch",
    "answer": "by",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "heiß",
    "answer": "hot",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "das Wort",
    "answer": "the word",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "aber",
    "answer": "but",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "was",
    "answer": "what",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "einige",
    "answer": "some",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "ist",
    "answer": "is",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "es",
    "answer": "it",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "Sie",
    "answer": "you",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "oder",
    "answer": "or",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "hatte",
    "answer": "had",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "die",
    "answer": "the",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "von",
    "answer": "of",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "zu",
    "answer": "to",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "und",
    "answer": "and",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "ein",
    "answer": "a",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "bei",
    "answer": "in",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "wir",
    "answer": "we",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "können",
    "answer": "can",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "aus",
    "answer": "out",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "andere",
    "answer": "other",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "waren",
    "answer": "were",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "die",
    "answer": "which",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "question": "tun",
    "answer": "do",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "question": "ihre",
    "answer": "their",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "question": "Zeit",
    "answer": "time",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "question": "wenn",
    "answer": "if",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "question": "werden",
    "answer": "will",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "question": "wie",
    "answer": "how",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "question": "sagte",
    "answer": "said",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "question": "ein",
    "answer": "an",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "question": "jeder",
    "answer": "each",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "question": "sagen",
    "answer": "tell",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 51,
    "question": "tut",
    "answer": "does",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 52,
    "question": "der Satz",
    "answer": "the set",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 53,
    "question": "drei",
    "answer": "three",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 54,
    "question": "wollen",
    "answer": "want",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 55,
    "question": "die Luft",
    "answer": "the air",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 56,
    "question": "gut",
    "answer": "well",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 57,
    "question": "auch",
    "answer": "also",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 58,
    "question": "spielen",
    "answer": "play",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 59,
    "question": "klein",
    "answer": "small",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 60,
    "question": "das Ende",
    "answer": "the end",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 61,
    "question": "setzen",
    "answer": "put",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 62,
    "question": "Zuhause",
    "answer": "home",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 63,
    "question": "lesen",
    "answer": "read",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 64,
    "question": "seits",
    "answer": "hand",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 65,
    "question": "der Hafen",
    "answer": "the port",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 66,
    "question": "groß",
    "answer": "large",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 67,
    "question": "buchstabieren",
    "answer": "spell",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 68,
    "question": "hinzufügen",
    "answer": "add",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 69,
    "question": "auch",
    "answer": "even",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 70,
    "question": "Lande",
    "answer": "land",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 71,
    "question": "hier",
    "answer": "here",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 72,
    "question": "muss",
    "answer": "must",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 73,
    "question": "groß",
    "answer": "big",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 74,
    "question": "hoch",
    "answer": "high",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 75,
    "question": "so",
    "answer": "such",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 76,
    "question": "folgen",
    "answer": "follow",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 77,
    "question": "Akt",
    "answer": "act",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 78,
    "question": "warum",
    "answer": "why",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 79,
    "question": "fragen",
    "answer": "ask",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 80,
    "question": "die Männer",
    "answer": "the men",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 81,
    "question": "die Veränderung",
    "answer": "the change",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 82,
    "question": "ging",
    "answer": "went",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 83,
    "question": "die Licht",
    "answer": "the light",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 84,
    "question": "die Art",
    "answer": "the kind",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 85,
    "question": "aus",
    "answer": "off",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 86,
    "question": "müssen",
    "answer": "need",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 87,
    "question": "das Haus",
    "answer": "the house",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 88,
    "question": "das Bild",
    "answer": "the picture",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 89,
    "question": "versuchen",
    "answer": "try",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 90,
    "question": "uns",
    "answer": "us",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 91,
    "question": "wieder",
    "answer": "again",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 92,
    "question": "das Tier",
    "answer": "the animal",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 93,
    "question": "der Punkt",
    "answer": "the point",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 94,
    "question": "die Mutter",
    "answer": "the mother",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 95,
    "question": "die Welt",
    "answer": "the world",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 96,
    "question": "in der Nähe von",
    "answer": "near",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 97,
    "question": "bauen",
    "answer": "build",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 98,
    "question": "selbst",
    "answer": "self",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 99,
    "question": "die Erde",
    "answer": "the earth",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  },
  {
    "id": 100,
    "question": "der Vater",
    "answer": "the father",
    "questionLanguage": "de",
    "answerLanguage": "en"
  }
]
